Guide to the William T. Cannady Architectural Projects Records, 1956-2018 MS 577
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VIII: Addendum III, 1959-2018
  - Greenway Tower color schemes, 2015-2016 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Cohen House [Rice University] Restoration Proposal, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Building Houston interview, 2016-04-14 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Perspective charts, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Atelier Rue de Sevres 35 by Le Corbusier, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Houston – An Architectural Guide, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    First Build Design
  - Just Plane Architecture" by Jeffrey Averill, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rough drafts of "Four Houses" (4)., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Architectural Design, 1970-08 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Architectural Design, Volume XLIII, 1972-04 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Design, Volume XLV, 1975-06 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Forum - Book review "New Schools for New Towns", 1969-09 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - AIA Perspective, 1993-01 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Proforma Project Feasibility Analysis, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Notebook, "London Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
  - Sketchbooks (8), 1979-2017 (Box 20)
  - The American Institute of Architects College of Fellows, History & Directory, 2000 (Box 20)
  - The American Institute of Architects College of Fellows, History and Directory of Texas Fellows, 2015 (Box 20)
  - Rough draft of "Four Houses", 1998 (Box 21)
  - Brochure - Lovett Square, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Thermal and Mechanical Building Documentation report - Rice ARCH 316, 2002-05-08 (Box 21)
  - Rice Village Mixed-Use building designs, 1983 (Box 21)